share the stage with you. Um,
it's great to be back here
in the valley again. See so
many familiar faces from
academia, my last tour of
service and from my first 100
days, which uh is just this
weekend. I've been looking
forward to this weekend. And
before I go further, I want to
thank Jeff Schmidt and his
team for the incredible
hospitality. Everybody here is
in debt to you and to your
colleagues here at the Federal
Reserve Bank of Kansas City.
Uh our Jeff Jeff, our thanks
uh to you and your team.
Now, he and the other planners
here have some recreation
options lined up for later
today. I'd advise you to be
very careful with your
choices. As I learned years
ago, you can take two
different kinds of hikes on
the trails around Jackson. I
can sum up my hikes with
former vice chairman Don Kohn
with two words. I survived.
These steely marathon death
marches revealed the sign of
Don that that I was not ready
for. But there's another kind
of hike. This one was with
former chairman Ben Bernanke,
another dear old colleague.
With Ben, it was a much more
leisurely pace, an easy stroll
along the wandering trails of
the Rockefeller Preserve. So
before setting out today, my
recommendation is do a
wellness check. Ask yourself,
is this a Kohn day or a
Bernanke day?
The best thing about this
gathering is that it helps us
all get out here to the
mountains and clear our minds
and think straight about our
world and our time. For me, it
feels like the right place and
the right audience for a real
engagement with the ideas that
matter most. Innovation, as
Kristen mentioned, is the
conference theme. And I
believe the public and the
markets understand that
innovations and the conduct of
Fed policy will help deliver
price stability alongside full
employment. So here's a quick
overview of what I'll cover in
my remarks this morning. You
can call it an outline. You
can call it a trail map.
But please just don't call it
forward guidance.
First, I'll touch on on a few
of the longer-term questions
we're asking at the Fed about
the latest general purpose
technology AI and where it
might take the economy. Then
I'll reflect a bit on the
practice of forward guidance
and the interaction between
the central bank and financial
markets. Next, I'll present
some of the key principles
that I believe should guide
the conduct of monetary
policy. And finally, I'll give
you my assessment of what's
happening in the economy.
So first, I think we should
try to prepare a bit for
future policy conjunctures.
With the unchanging picture of
the Tetons as our backdrop, we
are here